<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

  <!-- Imperial Style - General Cyrodiil culture -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Imperial</defName>
    <label>Imperial</label>
    <description>The refined Imperial style reflects the cosmopolitan culture of Cyrodiil's heartland, featuring elegant designs that blend practical functionality with imperial sophistication.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Colovian Style - Western Cyrodiil -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Colovian</defName>
    <label>Colovian</label>
    <description>The practical Colovian style embodies the martial traditions of western Cyrodiil's highlands, featuring earth tones and sturdy designs that reflect their straightforward, military-focused culture.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Nibenese Style - Eastern Cyrodiil -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Nibenese</defName>
    <label>Nibenese</label>
    <description>The sophisticated Nibenese style represents the cosmopolitan culture of eastern Cyrodiil, featuring rich colors and elegant designs that reflect their magical aptitude and mercantile traditions.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Imperial Legion Style - Military organization -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>ImperialLegion</defName>
    <label>Imperial Legion</label>
    <description>The disciplined Imperial Legion style features standardized military designs with red and gold colors, organized patterns, and symbols of Imperial authority reflecting the Empire's military might.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Breton Style -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Breton</defName>
    <label>Breton</label>
    <description>The scholarly Breton style embodies the magic-resistant people of High Rock, combining blue and silver academic colors with knightly designs that reflect their mixed elven-human heritage.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Nord Style -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Nord</defName>
    <label>Nord</label>
    <description>The hardy Nord style represents the fierce warriors of Skyrim, featuring grey and blue practical designs with Nordic patterns suited for harsh climates and independent living.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Redguard Style -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Redguard</defName>
    <label>Redguard</label>
    <description>The warrior Redguard style reflects the desert-dwelling fighters of Hammerfell, showcasing brown and bronze colors with curved weapon influences and designs adapted for harsh desert conditions.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Crown Style - Traditional Redguard nobility -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Crown</defName>
    <label>Crown</label>
    <description>The noble Crown style embodies the traditional aristocracy of Hammerfell, featuring rich ceremonial designs with ancient Yokudan motifs and symbols of noble heritage.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Forebear Style - Ra Gada descendants -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Forebear</defName>
    <label>Forebear</label>
    <description>The adaptable Forebear style represents the practical Ra Gada descendants, combining traditional Redguard elements with foreign influences and trade-focused aesthetics.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Na-Totambu Style - Ancient royal bloodlines -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>NaTotambu</defName>
    <label>Na-Totambu</label>
    <description>The refined Na-Totambu style reflects the most ancient noble bloodlines of Yokuda, featuring the purest traditional designs with elaborate ceremonial elements and royal symbolism.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

  <!-- Ansei Style - Sword-singer mysticism -->
  <StyleCategoryDef>
    <defName>Ansei</defName>
    <label>Ansei</label>
    <description>The mystical Ansei style represents the warrior-monks who practice sword-singing, featuring minimalist designs that emphasize the spiritual aspects of blade mastery and martial discipline.</description>
  </StyleCategoryDef>

</Defs>